{
    "subject": "Warren_Beatty",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "Reds__film_",
    "human_readable": "Warren Beatty acted in the film Reds.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9791664481163025,
            "question": "What role did Warren Beatty play in Reds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8676741719245911,
            "question": "Who acted in the film Reds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8131747245788574,
            "question": "What film did Warren Beatty act in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7408784031867981,
            "question": "Name a film featuring Warren Beatty."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6879234910011292,
            "question": "Is Warren Beatty known for acting in historical films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5438024401664734,
            "question": "What other famous actors appeared in Reds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5189141631126404,
            "question": "Did Warren Beatty direct any of his films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35478758811950684,
            "question": "When was the film Reds released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3492056429386139,
            "question": "What genre is the film Reds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.058313366025686264,
            "question": "Which movie is about John Reed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Warren Beatty acted in the film Reds.",
            "html": "yago_21490_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Reds?",
            "html": "yago_21490_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film Reds released?",
            "html": "yago_21490_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Warren Beatty direct any of his films?",
            "html": "yago_21490_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21490_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21490_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21490_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21490_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21490_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21490_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21490_170.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21490_176.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21490_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21490_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the answer to the query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Warren Beatty directed and starred in the film Reds, which suggests that he acted in the film. Specifically, it says that \"Warren Beatty as John Reed\" and also mentions his performance earned him an Academy Award nomination for Best Actor."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Warren Beatty acted in the film Reds.\" For example, multiple documents mention that Warren Beatty stars or starred as John Reed in the film Reds."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}